<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/">
  <channel>
    <title>truck-unblocked-game.github.io - Immerse Yourself in the Ultimate Gaming Experience at: Play Games Online for Endless Fun!</title>
    <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io</link>
    <description>Dive into a world of exhilarating online gaming at! Experience the thrill of playing games that captivate your senses and challenge your skills. Our platform offers a diverse selection of engaging, ensuring endless hours of entertainment for players of all levels</description>
    <generator>gnurt</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    <atom:link href="https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link>
    <sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
    <sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/hard-wheels-winter-2-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Hard Wheels Winter 2</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/hard-wheels-winter-2-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Control a monster truck and pass many challenging obstacles in Hard Wheels Winter 2. Get to the finish without crashing to earn co ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/eg6q3rmzewxldnbltt9180ncdi6gnt11/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Control a monster truck and pass many challenging obstacles in Hard Wheels Winter 2. Get to the finish without crashing to earn coins and upgrade the truck. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/hard-wheels-winter-2-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>303</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/truck-space-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Truck Space</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/truck-space-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Drive a large truck and park it into marked parking area in this 3D truck simulation game. Complete the task in shortest time to e ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/51ogd3a3zdwxdevpw2rvrxfqbwsiq3cu/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Drive a large truck and park it into marked parking area in this 3D truck simulation game. Complete the task in shortest time to earn more score points and unlock various achievements. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/truck-space-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>144</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/offroad-masters-challenge-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Offroad Masters Challenge</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/offroad-masters-challenge-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Would you like to embark on an adventure with your offroad truck over the continents, lands, and various countries with the Offroa ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/uuzsf91weppr2puldne8xyw5wnem04sn/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Would you like to embark on an adventure with your offroad truck over the continents, lands, and various countries with the Offroad Masters Challenge game? During the adventure, you can make a career with your offroad vehicle, you can join a free SUV driving adventure, or even, can crash your trucks in a huge offroad car crash arena! These cars can modifiable such as engine modifications, or tire modifications will be available. Join this adventure either in single player game mode, or in two player game mode. Let&#39;s go! ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/offroad-masters-challenge-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>447</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/jeep-drive-prisoner-transport-sim-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Jeep Drive Prisoner Transport Sim</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/jeep-drive-prisoner-transport-sim-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Have fun Jeep Drive Prisoner Transport Sim mobile ready in any android or iPhone device. Everything has been prepared for the tran ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/9hi5n0keo4523wdyx0hnlyn7jx9m726b/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Have fun Jeep Drive Prisoner Transport Sim mobile ready in any android or iPhone device. Everything has been prepared for the transfer of prisoners by the United States Army. Have fun operating an actual army prisoner vehicle. It&#39;s just the laws of physics at work in those army transport games. Recruited for US Army service. To complete training as a driver for the United States Army&#39;s prisoner transport and freight transport units. But it would be best if you had extensive prior expertise operating various military trucks. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/jeep-drive-prisoner-transport-sim-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>111</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/hummer-jeep-driving-sim-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Hummer Jeep Driving Sim</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/hummer-jeep-driving-sim-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Experience the excitement of hill driving games, bounce over severe ramps to conduct amazing Hummer Jeep tricks that could polish  ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/o44c97ra5t28ove6d3y6r5h82chsn50b/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Experience the excitement of hill driving games, bounce over severe ramps to conduct amazing Hummer Jeep tricks that could polish your incredible speeds off car racing talents, and go for enormous aerial vehicle stunts. Enjoy the true pleasure of hill-driving games. This off-road Hummer Jeep play is a great new take on the mountain driving or off-road jeep driving game genres. You won&#39;t believe the fun you&#39;ll have behind this 4x4 Insane Stunts Offroad Jeep automobile when you watch this crazy Hummer jeep racing video. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/hummer-jeep-driving-sim-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>255</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/truck-offroad-4x4-heavy-drive-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Truck Offroad 4x4 Heavy Drive</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/truck-offroad-4x4-heavy-drive-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ The thrill of 4x4 hill car driving in jeep games 4x4 lies in adding a new dimension to the objectives of offroad racing 3D and rev ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/07yuz5pxdc3h4yg5j1cd16qadqxvyshg/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;The thrill of 4x4 hill car driving in jeep games 4x4 lies in adding a new dimension to the objectives of offroad racing 3D and reviving the spirit of the original offline racing games.         &#xA;The journey, which may begin with hill adventures in tasks of 4x4 offroad jeep driver games, is progressively more brutal as you take on the role of the driver in jeep games 4x4. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/truck-offroad-4x4-heavy-drive-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>187</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/truck-town-parking-cars-2022-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Truck Town Parking Cars 2022</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/truck-town-parking-cars-2022-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ For every game, the UI is crucial. Parking game missions are available, and the UI makes it easy for you to fulfill them. In a sim ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/35j7mz8qp83mo4idbkculhy9ab5sqbo9/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;For every game, the UI is crucial. Parking game missions are available, and the UI makes it easy for you to fulfill them. In a similar vein, our interface makes it easy to complete a Cargo Truck Parking Challenge. You may begin by playing Advance Cargo Truck Parking gradually and work your way up to the basic Cargo Truck Parking game. Players will become irritated if the game moves slowly and the trucks can&#39;t move around freely. Your cargo truck driving abilities will be polished by our slick visuals, and you&#39;ll soon be able to play Parking games 3D flawlessly.    &#xA;You have never used a Cargo Truck Parking Simulator like the one we utilized. It doesn&#39;t matter if it&#39;s Parking Jam 3D or ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/truck-town-parking-cars-2022-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>312</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/jeep-driver-offroad-2022-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Jeep Driver Offroad 2022</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/jeep-driver-offroad-2022-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ This 4x4 Jeep game will provide hours of fun as you race across rolling hills and dense forests. The journeys you take in off-road ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/9uxarkbtw4jza0sryvg3fn51v79gs5or/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;This 4x4 Jeep game will provide hours of fun as you race across rolling hills and dense forests. The journeys you take in off-road driving games are filled with excitement from start to finish, be it a mountain climb or a mega car stunt. In SUV games, you can show off your skills as a master 4x4 stunt driver on challenging off-road tracks, narrow wooden bridges, streams, and mountains.    &#xA;Choose your favorite mountain jeep from among the other powerful off-road vehicles, and then get ready to embark on an exciting ride. The courses in the stunt Jeep game are choppy, jumpy, and full of unexpected difficulties.    &#xA;Participate in an exciting kart and Jeep game along the winding, narrow path that runs along the mountain. Along the route to the racing Jeep game, there are many checkpoints to stop at. Continue your expedition into the mud trucks by demonstrating that you are a master of the 4x4 stunt driving simulator.    &#xA;    &#xA;Be careful not to run out of fuel while climbing steep terrain in the offroad Jeep driving simulator; the longer you spend doing so, the more likely the energy will run out.    &#xA;The Challenging Mode aims to put your off-road driving skills to the test on incredibly tight tracks full of sharp turns and constantly shifting. A few small ramps can be used along the path for mudbug riding games. When driving a car, it&#39;s important to distinguish between exact and distracting routes. The checkpoints in the Jeep Wala game can provide you with some direction. When it comes to good performance, driving game masters will demonstrate how to control the vehicle in this mode to get to their destination in racing car games. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/jeep-driver-offroad-2022-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>435</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/monster-truck-supra-race-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Monster Truck Supra Race</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/monster-truck-supra-race-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Conquer your competition in intense head-to-head MONSTER TRUCK races that include fire-breathing monster trucks! The long-awaited  ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/wksztiwv7pkihgblrf8gi0hsk9s6hyl0/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Conquer your competition in intense head-to-head MONSTER TRUCK races that include fire-breathing monster trucks! The long-awaited release of the brand-spanking-new monster truck racing simulator game has finally here. Put yourself in the driver&#39;s seat of incredibly potent MONSTER TRUCKS, let the fire burn merrily, race the quickest 4x4 off-road monster vehicles, and treat your eyes to the spectacle of frantic, jump-filled racing through the breathtaking landscape of the American countryside, which is full of hills and valleys.  &#xA;Have you ever considered what it might be like to operate a monster truck in the real world? Great! Now is the time to put your driving abilities to the test and choose the type of vehicle that best suits your needs! Pick your favorite car and put it through its paces in the Boss Battle Races, Ranking Races, Limited Races, Extreme Races, Single Contest, and Daily Race modes! Compete against other people driving monster trucks online and work your way to the top of the leaderboards.  &#xA;  &#xA;Who has the most impressive vehicle? You do! Your goal is to win as many races as possible and establish yourself as the world&#39;s best new monster truck driver. The rural areas of the United States play host to some of the most intense battles between fire-breathing and ultimately formidable Monster Trucks. Experience a world that has been constructed to perfection, complete with picturesque hills, valleys, lakes, and railways. While you take in the breathtaking scenery, don&#39;t forget to keep an eye on the road, your competitors, and the next available ramp. The race is about to begin, so pick up your pace, partake in some drag racing, make a dash, and overcome the hill and the uphill.  &#xA;  &#xA;RACE, RAISE YOUR SPEED, AND BOUNCE  &#xA;This game will be at the top of your list of favorite games if you like playing games involving monster trucks, truck racing, or radio-controlled car rallies. On the one hand, you constantly worry about getting the highest monster truck performance and speed possible, but on the other hand, you want to obtain the best feasible truck design. So much for racing cars in a fun and simple arcade game! You may already be familiar with the concept of a monster truck, a pickup truck modified with a more extensive suspension and larger tires, often for recreational use. Discover an ideal solution that provides you with various alternatives to personalize and improve your flame-spewing vehicle and your armor. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/monster-truck-supra-race-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>189</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/alien-survival-shooter-2022-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Alien Survival Shooter 2022</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/alien-survival-shooter-2022-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ The shooting and driving game known as Alien Survival aims to make it through the onslaught of an alien invasion. Driving vehicles ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/7okgi29hycd7jobjdn79v7owc0kyzgtk/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;The shooting and driving game known as Alien Survival aims to make it through the onslaught of an alien invasion. Driving vehicles and trying to smash creatures or soldier aliens, parking your vehicle, collecting coincollectingect canisters, and many other missions exited can be fun on this great map. Some of the missions waiting for you to drive and shoot in great apocalypse maps include surviving enemy creatures, aliens firing a gun at you, driving vehicles and smashing creatures or soldier aliens, and so on.            &#xA;            &#xA;There is a survival game that involves an army of the undead and aliens, and they now control the globe. The blizzard survival game that we are familiar with includes activities related to survival games. The humans who hid in the underground bunkers were the only ones who had a chance of surviving the dinosaur survival game. Humanity rallied its troops and organized many smaller teams of highly skilled individuals. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/alien-survival-shooter-2022-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>375</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/hard-wheels-winter-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Hard Wheels Winter</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/hard-wheels-winter-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Drive a monster truck and pass many challenging obstacles in Hard Wheels Winter. Balance the heavy vehicle while driving over snow ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/axjmqqoar870odtnxqyfjlauc0z2u0r3/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Drive a monster truck and pass many challenging obstacles in Hard Wheels Winter. Balance the heavy vehicle while driving over snowy mountains and other cars. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/hard-wheels-winter-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>367</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/little-panda-truck-team-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Little Panda Truck Team</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/little-panda-truck-team-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Little Panda&#39;s truck Team is a very addictive game. In this game you need to help the truck team build the railway station and reb ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/4otkvotbs1dtwcr9rv9ejo36d6q669z0/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Little Panda&#39;s truck Team is a very addictive game. In this game you need to help the truck team build the railway station and rebuild the amusement park. You will use various kinds of trucks to do your works. Use a roller to flatten the road, use a forklift to lay formwork and tracks and use a crane to install parts for ferris wheels and roller coasters etc. While you are playing this game, the trucks also introduce themselves to you, which can reinforce your impression of the trucks. You will not only learn how the trucks work but also have lots of fun in this game. Isn&#39;t it amazing? Enjoy! ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/little-panda-truck-team-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>249</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/army-vehicle-transporting-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Army Vehicle Transporting</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/army-vehicle-transporting-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Army vehicle transporting refers to the specialized logistics and operations involved in moving military vehicles from one locatio ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/9bs240ik4h7sx6u3ftzis7b6jrvz7nhj/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Army vehicle transporting refers to the specialized logistics and operations involved in moving military vehicles from one location to another. This can include the movement of tanks, armored personnel carriers, jeeps, and other ground vehicles, both within a countrys borders and internationally. Transporting these vehicles requires careful planning, as their size, weight, and the need for security can present unique challenges. Whether its for training exercises, deployment to conflict zones, or humanitarian missions.&#xA;Website Developer  https://tr.kizi10.org ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/army-vehicle-transporting-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>465</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/monster-truck-offroad-stunts-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Monster truck Offroad Stunts</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/monster-truck-offroad-stunts-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Have you ever fantasized about taking a monster truck out for a spin on the open road and putting it through its paces in the real ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/4rlgw3k18f23ie6yzahw9xp5xcuqt0lg/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Have you ever fantasized about taking a monster truck out for a spin on the open road and putting it through its paces in the real world? Great! What exactly are you looking forward to? It&#39;s time to test your insane off-road driving talents and choose your preferred vehicle from the options provided in the category. Pick out your most capable car and put it through its paces in the Boss Battleground Stunts, Limited period Stunts, Extreme Stunts, and Single Contest! Drivers of monster trucks need to climb to the top of the seat and start their engines.    &#xA;    &#xA;You are free to play in whatever mode most appeals to you. Enjoy the adventurous and exciting levels with enjoyable gameplay, excellent visuals, and beautiful level design. During the gameplay of the monster truck off-the-road stunt game, you must collect all the money and earn additional bonus awards for meeting the aims and goals set for each stage.    &#xA;    &#xA;    &#xA;STUNT, RAISE YOUR SPEED, AND JUMP    &#xA;This game will be on your favorites on your games list if you are a significant fan of Monster truck games, drifting games, Truck games, or RC rally games. If any of those categories describe you, check out this game. It&#39;s high time, drivers, so hop in your monster trucks, pick out the one you like most, and rev up those engines! Demonstrate your speed in offroad drag racing and driving ability by crossing the finish line within the allotted time. You will be tested to see how determined you are to stand alone and battle, so prepare for the most violent Monster truck game yet! Now is the time to strap up and become a member of the drivers club that competes in off-road races using monster trucks. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/monster-truck-offroad-stunts-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>311</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/truck-offroad-drive-heavy-transport-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Truck Offroad Drive Heavy Transport</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/truck-offroad-drive-heavy-transport-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ The excitement of 4x4 hill cars being driven in 4x4 jeep games comes from giving the goals of offroad racing 3D with new dimension ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/qx19f0rfljwt9e7dkcs0xdaw4pw8zpzv/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;The excitement of 4x4 hill cars being driven in 4x4 jeep games comes from giving the goals of offroad racing 3D with new dimensions and bringing back the original offline racing games&#39; essence.         &#xA;As you assume the driver&#39;s position in 4x4 jeep games, the voyage, which may start with hill adventures in jobs, becomes increasingly cruel. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/truck-offroad-drive-heavy-transport-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>166</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/funny-mad-racing-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Funny Mad Racing</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/funny-mad-racing-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ This is the adventure of bouncy cars on the bouncy roads with the Funny Mad Racing game! The game consists of 40 levels various ca ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/oba2cgdvjemwvvloq5rnjr4ej7wjtksr/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;This is the adventure of bouncy cars on the bouncy roads with the Funny Mad Racing game! The game consists of 40 levels various cars and various surprising funny features that you will encounter during your adventure. You can play this great and fun hill-climbing adventure in 2 player mode besides of 1 player mode. Earn coins and unlock new features. Challenge a friend and double your fun! Let the adventure begin in the pixel world! ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/funny-mad-racing-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>146</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/truck-driver-snowy-roads-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Truck Driver Snowy Roads</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/truck-driver-snowy-roads-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Master truck drivers are ready to prove their skills on challenging snowy roads! Check out the Missions section or compete in Race ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/4u74l79cv9s3b9x7g4gj36ys4hp9px5s/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Master truck drivers are ready to prove their skills on challenging snowy roads! Check out the Missions section or compete in Races to unlock new and more powerful trucks.  There are 12  OffRoad Trucks in total in the Truck Driver: Snowy Roads  and they all have different styles, power and driving. If you want, you can also try your luck in the Free Drive section. Maybe there will be random missions where you can get coins! Choose the music you want from the radio and start the adventure! ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/truck-driver-snowy-roads-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>463</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/155-police-dragon-panzer-drive-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>155 Police Dragon Panzer Drive</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/155-police-dragon-panzer-drive-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ The first and only in the world!! Realistic Dragon Police Panzer!!           &#xA;The Most Realistic in the Field and With Its Own Uni ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/l3axzdhmojpazkbj2cngt8l91gaf32ve/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;The first and only in the world!! Realistic Dragon Police Panzer!!           &#xA;The Most Realistic in the Field and With Its Own Unique Dynamics that You have Never Experienced Before The Police Simulator Game 155 POLICE DRAGON PANZER SIMULATOR is Live!          &#xA;You will take charge against the riots and illegal demonstrations taking place in the city and with the POLICE DRAGON PANZER vehicle you will try to disperse the communities using water cannons and bring the situation under control. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/155-police-dragon-panzer-drive-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>352</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/little-panda-truck-team-build-the-city-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Little Panda Truck Team - Build The City</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/little-panda-truck-team-build-the-city-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Little Panda&#39;s truck Team is a very addictive game. In this game, you need to help the truck team build the railway station and re ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/1h55lxp1c77doz9zl99cqcw0yf5xkbk3/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Little Panda&#39;s truck Team is a very addictive game. In this game, you need to help the truck team build the railway station and rebuild the amusement park. You will use various kinds of trucks to do your work. Use a roller to flatten the road, a forklift to lay formwork and tracks, and use a crane to install parts for Ferris wheels and roller coasters, etc. While you are playing this game, the trucks also introduce themselves to you, which can reinforce your impression of the trucks. You will not only learn how the trucks work but also have lots of fun in this game. Isn&#39;t it amazing? Enjoy! ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/little-panda-truck-team-build-the-city-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>490</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/multiplayer-car-crash-simulator-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Multiplayer Car Crash Simulator</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/multiplayer-car-crash-simulator-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ In this thrilling online car game, join other players in real-time and collide on the city streets! Showcase your skills by overco ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/xcqyr29d7xsdmtw92nnkt4i7n3ov2xf5/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;In this thrilling online car game, join other players in real-time and collide on the city streets! Showcase your skills by overcoming the citys destructive obstacles. With detailed urban landscapes and interactive social features, become the ultimate car driver in this adrenaline-pumping game! ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/multiplayer-car-crash-simulator-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>395</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/monster-truck-racing-battlegrounds-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Monster Truck Racing Battlegrounds</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/monster-truck-racing-battlegrounds-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Welcome to Monster Truck Racing Battleground game.&#xA;Monster trucks race to win on a racetrack.&#xA;You need to win the race using the B ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/ywxzmb1cg0sh15cjhn1aas3kbvlbmnsi/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Welcome to Monster Truck Racing Battleground game.&#xA;Monster trucks race to win on a racetrack.&#xA;You need to win the race using the Blue Monster Truck.&#xA;Other Monster Trucks are driven by artificial intelligence.&#xA;Think you can beat the Artificial Intelligence Monster Trucks?&#xA;Good luck to you in this race. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/monster-truck-racing-battlegrounds-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>279</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/monster-trucks-stunts-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Monster Trucks Stunts</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/monster-trucks-stunts-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Monster Trucks Stunts is an adrenaline-pumping, action-packed mobile game that puts you in the drivers seat of powerful, roaring m ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/p6y6szhufhrmdrpwkdclke8hqhj7oasw/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Monster Trucks Stunts is an adrenaline-pumping, action-packed mobile game that puts you in the drivers seat of powerful, roaring monster trucks. Get ready to unleash your inner daredevil as you embark on an exciting journey of stunt-filled mayhem! Take on various challenging levels across diverse landscapes, from sprawling urban cities to rugged off-road terrains, each designed to test your driving skills to the limit.&#xA;Perform jaw-dropping stunts like gravity-defying jumps, thrilling flips. Website Developer ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/monster-trucks-stunts-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>257</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/off-road-truck-cargo-delivery-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Off Road Truck Cargo Delivery</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/off-road-truck-cargo-delivery-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Handle cargoes carefully without dropping them ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/q1zxul8dcmhw50oerp7vox6uxmb1lopx/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Handle cargoes carefully without dropping them ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/off-road-truck-cargo-delivery-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>113</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/cargo-truck-transport-hunt-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Cargo Truck: Transport &amp; Hunt</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/cargo-truck-transport-hunt-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Are you ready for a wild adventure with Cargo Truck: Transport &amp; Hunt, a simulation game that combines driving and hunting? The zo ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/ng2igdvp92xohmlehl315mwqe3wt9caq/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Are you ready for a wild adventure with Cargo Truck: Transport &amp; Hunt, a simulation game that combines driving and hunting? The zoo animals have escaped and you are the only one who can catch them! Drive your truck across the city and use your sniper gun to hunt down the animals, from leopards to elephants. But be careful, they are fast and furious! You have to bring them back to the zoo safely and quickly. Cargo Truck: Transport &amp; Hunt is a game that will challenge your skills and nerves. Don’t miss this exciting game! Have fun! ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/cargo-truck-transport-hunt-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>191</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/monster-truck-wheels-winter-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Monster Truck Wheels Winter</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/monster-truck-wheels-winter-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Play monster truck driving game Monster Truck Wheels Winter edition. Winter is a good season to test your trucks off-road abilitie ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/bh69guvcxigqbpmsg4n6pa8bbrrvzfhn/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Play monster truck driving game Monster Truck Wheels Winter edition. Winter is a good season to test your trucks off-road abilities. So put large off-road wheels on the truck and get ready for a crazy ride over snowy mountains, vehicles, bridges and other obstacles on the track. Try to keep the monster truck balanced and complete the track as fast as possible to earn more score points and unlock various achievements. Each level gets harder, so be patient and explore what driving strategy is best for current obstacle. Play this cool monster truck driving game Monster Truck Wheels Winter online for free on any mobile device or computer. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/monster-truck-wheels-winter-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>52</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/racing-truck-difference-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Racing Truck Difference</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/racing-truck-difference-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Car racing is a fascinating sight, but it is especially interesting when heavy vehicles - trucks, are accepted in competitions. To ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/5pgr9c4ixjctg8lju3bul1y900urn4dh/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Car racing is a fascinating sight, but it is especially interesting when heavy vehicles - trucks, are accepted in competitions. To manage such engines, skills are required and our riders definitely have them. Otherwise, we would not get such colorful and interesting photos that are now in our game Racing Truck Differences. We specifically selected some of the most impressive ones and suggest you find the differences between pairs of almost identical frames. Search time is limited, the scale will move down, steadily decreasing.  Website Developer https://speedcargames.com/ ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/racing-truck-difference-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>143</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/monster-truck-wheels-2-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Monster Truck Wheels 2</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/monster-truck-wheels-2-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ In Monster Truck Wheels 2, youll be driving a heavy SUV, and weve already prepared fifteen different tracks. Do not rely on simpli ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/qf7gm6lcd394yd54umnpifqqejrie2kg/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;In Monster Truck Wheels 2, youll be driving a heavy SUV, and weve already prepared fifteen different tracks. Do not rely on simplicity and ease, the tracks, from the very first stages it will be super difficult. You need to climb pyramids of different sizes, drive along bridges, drive into containers and standing cars. Your jeep is not very stable and can roll over easily. Wisely adjust the brake and gas, if necessary, back up in order to overcome the next obstacles with acceleration. Distances on the levels are short, but quite difficult, be careful and careful. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/monster-truck-wheels-2-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>97</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/offroad-army-transporter-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Offroad Army Transporter</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/offroad-army-transporter-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ If you like to play car driving simulation games, you will like this vehicle driving simulation game called US Army Vehicle Transp ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/pfguvprgeyctw1wsrqdozw1dajz3ldui/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;If you like to play car driving simulation games, you will like this vehicle driving simulation game called US Army Vehicle Transporter Truck. It is managed for you to transport both tanks and cars to the pointed military base with a provided truck at each level. Before transporting missions, you usually need to drive the tanks and cars on or off the truck. Keep ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/offroad-army-transporter-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>119</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/heavy-crane-driving-simulator-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Heavy Crane Driving Simulator</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/heavy-crane-driving-simulator-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Heavy Crane Simulator is a very interesting simulation and real driving game with addictive gameplay and a 3D art style. If drivin ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/6kpg6ueiq54ccpsoi1fq79acznbgqy3l/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Heavy Crane Simulator is a very interesting simulation and real driving game with addictive gameplay and a 3D art style. If driving ordinary cars and motorcycles can no longer satisfy you, then this game is undoubtedly your best A good choice, but also a brand new game attempt. Your task is to park the crane at the designated location. It sounds very simple, but this is not an easy task, because driving a large crane requires extremely high driving skills, and you need to carefully observe the road conditions and surrounding obstacles. Are you ready to complete the parking task? ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/heavy-crane-driving-simulator-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>32</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/monster-truck-hill-driving-2d-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Monster Truck Hill Driving 2D</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/monster-truck-hill-driving-2d-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Crazy Hill: Driving is an exhilarating and fast-paced racing game that takes you on a wild journey through a variety of challengin ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/ysuraijixtlrejvvj58tk8psw7mmozzb/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Crazy Hill: Driving is an exhilarating and fast-paced racing game that takes you on a wild journey through a variety of challenging terrains. Strap yourself in and get ready for an adrenaline-pumping experience as you navigate treacherous hills, steep slopes, and unpredictable obstacles in a bid to conquer the craziest tracks ever created.&#xA;In Crazy Hill: Driving, you take on the role of a daring and skilled driver, determined to prove your mettle on the most unforgiving landscapes. The game offers a vast array of vehicles to choose from, each with its own unique characteristics, ensuring that every race feels fresh and exciting. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/monster-truck-hill-driving-2d-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>383</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/truck-transporter-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Truck Transporter</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/truck-transporter-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ In the game Truck Transporter you will drive a truck of the company KamAZ. Your task is to deliver a certain cargo to the final po ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/t8tex1grm1og4jshc53tfecg3eseivi4/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;In the game Truck Transporter you will drive a truck of the company KamAZ. Your task is to deliver a certain cargo to the final point at each level. But first you have to download it with a special tap. Capture objects and send them to the back. Try to keep them as tight as possible so that they do not fall out during the trip. And the road will be quite difficult. If you carry at least eighty percent of your cargo, your trip in Truck Transporter will be counted. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/truck-transporter-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>313</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/tractor-challenge-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Tractor Challenge</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/tractor-challenge-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ In the new Tractor Challenge game, you have to conduct field trials of new tractor models that will soon go on sale. Selecting a s ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/fs5o27zuvaq3topxuqk7tsbry3nuvfu7/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;In the new Tractor Challenge game, you have to conduct field trials of new tractor models that will soon go on sale. Selecting a specific tractor model you will see it in front of you on the screen. The tractor will stand on the road. By pushing the gas pedal, you will ride it on a road with a difficult terrain, gradually gaining speed. You will need to deftly drive a vehicle to overcome many dangerous sections of the road and even make ski jumps. The main thing is not to let the tractor roll over, because then you will fail the test. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/tractor-challenge-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>263</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/real-truck-parking-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Real Truck Parking</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/real-truck-parking-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ In Real Truck Parking you have to drive a big truck without a body. The task is to drive along specially designated paths that are ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/tnggqzqcrzsl9odrjv32qkysanf370su/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;In Real Truck Parking you have to drive a big truck without a body. The task is to drive along specially designated paths that are fenced with concrete blocks and containers and get to a rectangle drawn on the asphalt - this is the parking lot. In the upper left corner you will see a timer, it will start counting down a second, which means that you need to have time to park the truck before the time is up. The level will be successfully completed if you hit the fence in the parking lot. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/real-truck-parking-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>380</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/3d-truck-parking-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>3D Truck Parking</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/3d-truck-parking-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ 3D truck driving simulator with realistic physics and smooth gameplay. Drive the trailer truck through large city environment and  ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/ez0ge56azy3k44c198dej21bsmjawl5i/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;3D truck driving simulator with realistic physics and smooth gameplay. Drive the trailer truck through large city environment and park it into marked area. Use the camera to do this. It will help you to see the car from different angles. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/3d-truck-parking-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>135</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/monster-truck-wheels-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Monster Truck Wheels</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/monster-truck-wheels-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ You in the game Monster Truck Wheels will be the driver who will manage them. At the beginning of the game you sit behind the whee ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/q42nbv0ildyhi6nsdhvi9djn5fabfufh/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;You in the game Monster Truck Wheels will be the driver who will manage them. At the beginning of the game you sit behind the wheel of the monster truck and bring it to the starting line. On a signal, you are going to speed ahead. On your way you will see obstacles of different levels of difficulty. You are driving a car will need to either overcome them at speed, or slowed down to hold the car carefully so as not to let it turn over. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/monster-truck-wheels-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>176</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/monster-truck-4x4-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Monster Truck 4x4</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/monster-truck-4x4-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Your monster truck will have a difficult 4x4 Monster track. It&#39;s not just off-road, it&#39;s just the easiest way to drive. A number o ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/h4sk8wa695din59peeddgny55b4s27xt/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Your monster truck will have a difficult 4x4 Monster track. It&#39;s not just off-road, it&#39;s just the easiest way to drive. A number of different obstacles were installed on the hilly terrain: log jumps, refrigerated trucks, metal bridges, concrete rings and other buildings. In addition, wheels, wooden boxes and forgotten traffic cones are lying on the road. The task at the level is to go through the track without an accident and stop near the finish flag. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/monster-truck-4x4-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>26</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/pickup-cargo-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Pickup Cargo</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/pickup-cargo-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Drive a pickup truck on dirty and hilly roads and deliver various cargo to the customers houses. Drive the truck carefully and avo ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/0ovccdrjotdrm6bj2irsb20j6wfazb7o/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Drive a pickup truck on dirty and hilly roads and deliver various cargo to the customers houses. Drive the truck carefully and avoid losing too much of your cargo. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/pickup-cargo-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>160</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/tractor-trial-2-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Tractor Trial 2</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/tractor-trial-2-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Play as a farmer who got tired of the hard daily work at the farm. Jump into the tractor and test its off-road capabilities. Drive ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/4zlg30hno8g57ytqd30pqn1hvramzfbn/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Play as a farmer who got tired of the hard daily work at the farm. Jump into the tractor and test its off-road capabilities. Drive up large hills and pass various obstacles to make to the finish. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/tractor-trial-2-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>115</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/mad-truck-driving-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Mad Truck Driving</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/mad-truck-driving-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Do you love driving trucks and crushing cars? Then you will enjoy Mad Truck Driving, the best 2D driving game ever! This game lets ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/pj997lwxryci1jh3fbsa3jf1kttsp5ut/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Do you love driving trucks and crushing cars? Then you will enjoy Mad Truck Driving, the best 2D driving game ever! This game lets you drive a powerful truck through various obstacles and challenges! You will be amazed by the interesting graphics and exciting sound effects! Don’t worry about the cars in front of you, just smash them with your truck! Your truck is unstoppable! But can you overcome the different obstacles and complete the levels? Try Mad Truck Driving now and start your adventure! ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/mad-truck-driving-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>94</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/hillside-drive-master-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Hillside Drive Master</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/hillside-drive-master-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Embark on an exhilarating 3D truck delivery adventure with Hillside Drive Master. Your mission is to transport 3 stickmen across v ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/mapfm8t3unz663vwmw69nsttog7a0uq4/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Embark on an exhilarating 3D truck delivery adventure with Hillside Drive Master. Your mission is to transport 3 stickmen across various levels to the peak of the mountain. Along the challenging journey, feel free to toss the stickmen - as long as you reach the finish line. Collect coins along the way to unlock mystery gifts for added fun. If youre ready to take on the Hillside Drive Master challenge, then hop into this 3D trucking experience and get ready for thrills and excitement like never before! ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/hillside-drive-master-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>200</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/cargo-truck-offroad-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Cargo Truck Offroad</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/cargo-truck-offroad-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Venture into the wild terrains with Cargo Truck Offroad! In this thrilling driving simulation game, players are put behind the whe ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/bqypgh7mizibuctv597a3akm4cl3fd2d/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Venture into the wild terrains with Cargo Truck Offroad! In this thrilling driving simulation game, players are put behind the wheel of a rugged cargo truck, tasked with delivering goods across challenging offroad landscapes. Navigate through muddy trails, steep mountain paths, and treacherous river crossings, all while ensuring your precious cargo remains intact. As you progress, earn rewards to upgrade your truck or unlock more challenging routes. With realistic physics, immersive graphics, and dynamic weather conditions, every journey promises a unique adventure. Website Developer  https://de.kizi10.org ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/cargo-truck-offroad-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>452</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/heavy-tractor-towing-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Heavy Tractor Towing</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/heavy-tractor-towing-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Here is a tractor-driving simulation game. With 3D snow mountain roads, you need to transport the bus or cargo containers by drivi ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/8vegqqzw0d9k0lj0e9y81afxv2wco261/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Here is a tractor-driving simulation game. With 3D snow mountain roads, you need to transport the bus or cargo containers by driving a tractor on time. Try to keep balanced and drive stably. Have a good time! ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/heavy-tractor-towing-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>473</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/trailer-truck-parking-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Trailer Truck Parking</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/trailer-truck-parking-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Do you enjoy playing parking games, friends? You can play a fun truck parking game called Trailer Truck Parking thanks to Jhurr.co ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/xk33o0aj2l8gos5cin3qng1pj5aymdzq/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Do you enjoy playing parking games, friends? You can play a fun truck parking game called Trailer Truck Parking thanks to Jhurr.com. Enjoy driving your truck around the crowded parking lots and park it in the designated spot without hitting any other vehicles or objects. Drive carefully and methodically to the parking space, take in the thrilling levels, park your truck in various settings, and prove yourself to be a pro truck driver. Play further driving games at Jhurr.com. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/trailer-truck-parking-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>305</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/truck-simulator-skibidi-toilet-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Truck Simulator Skibidi Toilet</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/truck-simulator-skibidi-toilet-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Before you start your multi-million dollar logistics company, you will first have to complete quick jobs using provided trucks. Yo ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/t6vmzx5aubxgwqnocbruc9n01c4q1f9b/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Before you start your multi-million dollar logistics company, you will first have to complete quick jobs using provided trucks. You will have to earn at least before buying your first truck.&#xA;As the player completes jobs and levels up, they will unlock skills. Skills can be used to upgrade fuel efficiency and long distance cargoes as well as unlocking hazardous, fragile, and important deliveries. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/truck-simulator-skibidi-toilet-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>301</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/crazy-car-transport-truck-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Crazy car transport truck</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/crazy-car-transport-truck-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ In this Advance Truck driving game your task is to move loads of freight things starting with one spot then onto the next inside c ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/1rrpv2bnffkj89bpvjszjwyyyj0ft8mo/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;In this Advance Truck driving game your task is to move loads of freight things starting with one spot then onto the next inside city. You need to appreciate off-road Driving game while driving the truck in mountains valleys and escalate the rush of slope ascending test on troublesome rough terrain tracks in police car driver challenge game. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/crazy-car-transport-truck-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>201</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/us-army-vehicle-transport-truck-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Us Army Vehicle Transport Truck</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/us-army-vehicle-transport-truck-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ US Army Vehicle Transporter Truck Simulator:Army Game is one the finest army oil tanker truck game of us army transport which has  ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/7mn9oztt6vibflrgzdvb6tfswa32685y/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;US Army Vehicle Transporter Truck Simulator:Army Game is one the finest army oil tanker truck game of us army transport which has series of challenges as Vehicle transport games offer you multiple challenging army vehicle transport missions to make you us army transporter in short time period by providing you us army transport long lists of practical cargo army driving missions. Most of your army is engaged in various expeditions across all borders and it is in need of professional truck transporter who can drive army cargo truck. Take the charge of cargo truck drive on your shoulders and provide all required vehicles to your army through car ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/us-army-vehicle-transport-truck-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>213</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/full-ball-puzzle-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Full Ball Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/full-ball-puzzle-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Full Ball is an arcade game where you have to fill the truck bed with balls. You have to wait for the right time to fill the movin ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/d3dxq8n2nhfyl97eth0mikq3lht8txj5/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Full Ball is an arcade game where you have to fill the truck bed with balls. You have to wait for the right time to fill the moving truck crates with balls and release the balls at the right time. You can release the balls waiting in a bell by left clicking on the mouse.&#xA;Full Ball brings together trendy arcade games and oldest brain teasers.&#xA;Full Ball is a free arcade game that you can play on web and mobile browsers. Includes 16 different language translations. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/full-ball-puzzle-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>226</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/offroad-cargo-truck-driver-3d-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Offroad Cargo Truck Driver 3D</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/offroad-cargo-truck-driver-3d-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ The people who love truck games, then this is the place to be. Welcome to new “Offroad Cargo Truck Driver:Uphill Logging Truck 3 ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/v7x5q1vny9zj15vy0gi4yg4e57cycijw/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;The people who love truck games, then this is the place to be. Welcome to new “Offroad Cargo Truck Driver:Uphill Logging Truck 3D”. The best free truck game of 2023 in 3d truck driving games. Your job is to transport important truck cargo in this Offroad Cargo Truck Transport Driving. Trust me Truck Driver Cargo isn’t as simple as it looks. You will have to drive the Offroad Cargo Truck in a hill side environment. Drive Indian Truck and American Trucks in Cargo Transport Simulator with much care on off road to help companies who want to deliver goods at the appropriate time. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/offroad-cargo-truck-driver-3d-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>190</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/top-down-truck-racing-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Top Down Truck Racing</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/top-down-truck-racing-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Top Down Truck Racing is an exciting and fast-paced top-down racing game that puts you behind the wheel of a variety of powerful b ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/8z7pkpe6l4cx2cauofbkq84izgqjpf8t/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Top Down Truck Racing is an exciting and fast-paced top-down racing game that puts you behind the wheel of a variety of powerful big-rigs. The game features a range of diverse and engaging maps, spanning from desert canyons, bustling cityscapes, slippery ice roads, to dense forest trails. Each map is intricately designed with unique characteristics that can be mastered to gain an edge in races. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/top-down-truck-racing-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>458</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/parking-mania-3d-unblocked-game.html</guid>
      <title>Parking Mania 3D</title>
      <link>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/parking-mania-3d-unblocked-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Parking Mania is an exciting online game that challenges your skills in navigating through a crowded parking lot to remove your ca ]]&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;![CDATA[ &lt;img src=&#34;https://img.gamemonetize.com/y291x1f70esg0fikq3jy4lrjyp5ihk9s/512x384.jpg&#34;&gt;Parking Mania is an exciting online game that challenges your skills in navigating through a crowded parking lot to remove your car from its tight spot. The game features multiple levels, each with its own set of obstacles and challenges to overcome. To successfully remove your car from the parking lot, you must carefully maneuver around other parked cars, avoid obstacles, and make your way to the exit.  With its engaging gameplay, colorful graphics, and challenging levels, Parking Mania is a game that will keep you entertained and engaged for hours. Whether you&#39;re a fan of puzzle games, simulation games, or just looking for a fun way to pass the time, this game is sure to provide a fun and exciting experience. ]]&gt;</content:encoded>
      <comments>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/parking-mania-3d-unblocked-game.html/#respond</comments>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://truck-unblocked-game.github.io/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>195</slash:comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>